globalmarket.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy

## The Information We Collect

Registration Information: At the time you register to become a Registered Member of the Site, you will be asked to provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business **("Registration Information").**

Publishing Information: If you submit any information to GlobalMarket to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalog and Trade Leads Profile, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information **("Publishing Information").**

Statistical Information: In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Members, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth. **("Statistical Information").**

Registration Information: Publishing Information, Statistical Information and any information we may collect from you through the use of cookies (see Section 5 below), or any other means, shall collectively be referred to as **"Collected Information".**

## How We May Use Information

General: We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Members. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Members. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

Registration Information: We may use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which GlobalMarket determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.

Publishing Information: All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to GlobalMarket becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us.

Statistical Information: We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site, and to enhance our Site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We may provide Statistical Information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.

## Disclosure of Information

We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of GlobalMarket, our Members, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

If we have reason to believe that a Member is in breach of the Terms of Use Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such Member's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to GlobalMarket or others.

## Cookies

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information or Publishing Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Members; research visiting patterns and help target advertisements based on Member interests; assist our partners to track Member visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions.

Third parties also serve or use cookies through this website. These cookies do not carry any personally identifiable information and are used to show our advertisements on various sites across the Internet. The third party remarketing vendors concerned use cookies to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. 

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you may be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site may be unavailable.

## Minors

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

## Security Measures

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

As a Registered Member, your Registration Information and Publishing Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., Member ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact GlobalMarket in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that GlobalMarket return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in GlobalMarket's possession. This Privacy Policy was last amended on February 28, 2007.

## Correcting Your Information

You can access, view and edit your Registration Information and Publishing Information (if any) through your Account with GlobalMarket. To update or correct such information, please click here.

## Your feedback

GlobalMarket welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may responses to call our buyer service center +86-20-86002299 or send your comments to our Buyer Service Executive [buyerservice@globalmarket.com](mailto:buyerservice@globalmarket.com). By postal mail, you can write to our headquarter: No.28 & No.33, Yunshan North Street, No.1128 Baiyun South Ave, Baiyun District, Guangzhou, P.R.C. 510420 

## Choice and Opt-Out 

When you subscribe our email services, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service. We will send you e mail alerts for new products & manufacturer information, features, industry & tradeshow updates, contests, events of interest. Such alerts may include marketing information about GlobalMarket.com, our subsidiaries or selected business partners. If you no longer wish to receive GlobalMarket's promotional communications and email services, you may "opt-out" of receiving them any time by an easy automated unsubscribe link, which included in each email we send to you. If you have any trouble in unsubscribing, you can contact our Buyer Service Executive by [buyerservice@globalmarket.com](mailto:buyerservice@globalmarket.com).
